Guide to the Church League of America Collection of the Research Files of Counterattack, the Wackenhut Corporation, and Karl Baarslag TAM.148
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Counterattack Research Files, 1928-1967
  - Subseries V: Individuals, 1931-1960
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Koestler, Arthur; Klineberg, Dr. Otto; Isaacs, Stanley M.; Finney, Mrs. Burnham; Cottone, Benedict P.; Conte, Richard; Compton, Dr. Karl T.] (14-0-1231 to 14-0-1237), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Vorse, Mary Heaton; Tchou, Colonel M. Thomas; Schwartz, Louis B.; Primus, Pearl; Plotkin, Harry; Piastro, Michel; Lerner, Max] (14-0-1238 to 14-0-1244), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Williams, Jay; Russell, Bertrand; Roberson, Mason; O'Donnell, Mary King; Eisenberg, Frances; Bay, Howard; Weber, Bill; Walsh, J. Raymond] (14-0-1245 to 14-0-1253), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lowell, Benjamin; Loeb, Philip; Hewitt, Alan; Fadiman, Clifton; Everett, Edward H.; Conway, Joseph; Picon, Molly; Winters, Lawrence] (14-0-1254 to 14-0-1261), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [King, Jean; Stout, Rex; Segal, Bernard; Osman, Arthur; Carnes, Nick; Paley, Jack; Livingston, David; Roosevelt, Eleanor; Mayer, Lawrence A.] (14-0-1262 to 14-0-1272), 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Reports on Potential Subjects of Inquiries, Arranged Alphabetically] (14-0-1273 to 14-0-1336), undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Smith, Henry Ladd; Sterling, Philip; Levine, Ruth; Blaine, Martin; Cooper, Herman C.; Conway, Curt; Norton, Robert; Christopherson, Vernon A.; Lardner, Ringgold Wilmer, Jr.] (14-0-1337 to 14-0-1347), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Rosenberg, Dave; Blum, Manny; Russo, Mike; Siepmann, Charles A.; Tyler, Ralph; Smythe, Dallas W.; Siegel, Seymour N.; Taylor, Telford] (14-0-1348 to 14-0-1355), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Ferrer, Jose; Gray, Barry; Lyon, Peter; Sondergaard, Hester; Hunt, Marsha; Baldwin, Roger N.; Drake, Alfred; Ives, Burl; Berger, Henry] (14-0-1356 to 14-0-1365), 1948-1951 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Wilson, Teddy; Robinson, Edward G.; Jaffe, Sam; Holliday, Judy; Proelick, Samuel; Friedman, Charles] (14-0-1366 to 14-0-1371), 1949-1951 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Adler, Larry; Allen, Marilyn R.; Anderson, Marian; Albaum, Professor Harry; Aronoff, Jacob Broches] (14-0-1372 to 14-0-1376A), 1950 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["B" and Chaplin, Charlie] (14-0-1376 to 14-0-1448), 1942, 1946-1951 (Box 14, Folder 17-18)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["C"] (14-0-1449 to 14-0-1474), 1941, 1946-1950 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Mixed "C" and "D"] (14-0-1475A to 1499), 1937, 1947-1951 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["D"] (14-0-1500 to 14-0-1546), 1947-1951 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Dilling, Elizabeth and "E"] (14-0-1547 to 14-0-1565), 1947-1951 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["F"] (14-0-1566 to 14-0-1623), 1946-1951 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Ferjencik, General Mikulas and Milada; "G"] (14-0-1624 to 14-0-1682), 1948-1951 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lists of Individuals in Entertainment Industry; Hollywood Reds are "On the Run" and Red Stars Over Hollywood (Irish Edition); Flynn, John T.; Fagan, Myron C.; Hoover, J. Edgar; Menjou, Adolphe] (14-0-1683 to 14-0-1684), 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["H"] (14-0-1685 to 14-0-1760), 1946-1951 (Box 14, Folder 26-27)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["I" and "J"] (14-0-1761 to 14-0-1778), 1948-1950 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Hagberg, Gene; "K"] (14-0-1779 to 14-0-1832), 1947-1951 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["L"] (14-0-1833 to 14-0-1887), 1936, 1944-1951 (Box 14, Folder 30-31)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Swadesh, Professor Max; Ross, Paul L.; Hewitt, Alan; Pinter, Anthony; Leonardi, Frank and Rose] (14-0-1888 to 14-0-1892), 1948-1951 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["M"] (14-0-1893 to 14-0-1907), 1948-1950 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Untermeyer, Louis; Mamoulian, Rouben; Rodgers, Richard; Russell, Rosalind; Logan, Joshua; Knox, Alexander; Cagney, James] (14-0-1908 to 14-0-1914), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Carson, Greer; Hammerstein, Oscar II; Hall, George; Johnson, Dorothy; Overstreet, Bonaro W.; Campbell, William; Glenn, William Melbourne] (14-0-1915 to 14-0-1923], 1951 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["M"] (14-0-1924 to 14-0-1986), 1935, 1946-1951 (Box 14, Folder 36-37)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["N"] (14-0-1987 to 14-0-2007), 1948-1950 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["O"] (14-0-2008 to 14-0-2028), 1945-1950 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["P"] (14-0-2029 to 14-0-2073), 1946-1951 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["P"] (14-0-2074 to 14-0-2087), 1947-1950 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Quinn, T. Vincent and "R"] (14-0-2087A to 14-0-2167), 1946-1951 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["S"] (14-0-2168 to 14-0-2199), 1947-1951 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["A" through "F"] (14-0-2200 to 14-0-2246), 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["G" through "K"] (14-0-2247 to 14-0-2269), 1949-1951 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["L" through "M"] (14-0-2270 to 14-0-2299), 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["R" through "Z"] (14-0-2300 to 14-0-2338), 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lists of Names and Short Reports from Research Department; List of Prize Winners and Exhibitors from Graphic Arts Exhibition for Peace and Progress] (14-0-2339 to 14-0-2343), 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Rubinstein, Artur; Golden, John; Massey, Raymond; Sherrill, Henry K.; Mumford, Lewis] (14-0-2344 to 14-0-2349), 1951 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["S"] (14-0-2350 to 14-0-2388), 1931, 1947-1951 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["T" and Hammerstein, Oscar II] (14-0-2389 to 14-0-2424), 1948-1951 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["U" and "V"] (14-0-2425 to 14-0-2443), 1948-1950 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Wahrhaftig, Samuel L.; Wagner, Robert F., Jr.; Wadleigh, Henry Julian; Martin, Edward; O'Neil, James F.; Roberts, Eleanor; Canhon, Edith] (14-0-2444 to 14-0-2449), 1947-1950 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lists of Possible Communist Party Members, Anti-Communists, and "New York Employees Not Returning After Strike"] (14-0-2452 to 14-0-2454), 1949-1951 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals ["W" through "Z"] (14-0-2455 to 14-0-2515), 1947-1950 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Davis, Bette; Forman, Harrison; Osborne, Dr. Ernest G.; Harris, Robert E.; Gomez, Manuel; Bridges, Lloyd; Budenz, Louis] (14-0-2516 to 14-0-2524), 1947-1951 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Alter, Victor; Erlich, Henrich; Robbins, Jerome; Stewart, Paul; Gilford, Jack; Dekker, Albert; Corwin, Norman; Holliday, Judy; Vandercook, John W.] (14-0-2525 to 14-0-2542), 1943, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [March, Fredric; Levenson, Sam; Drake, Alfred; Houseman, John; Shaw, Artie; Josephson, Barney; Kramer, Stanley; Deutscher, Isaac; Viereck, Peter; Rosenzweig, Abe] (14-0-2543 to 14-0-2553), 1941, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Schoenberg, Arnold; Benoit-Levy, Jean; Josephson, Leon; Eisler, Gerhardt; Fagan, Myron C.; Hellman, Lillian; Miller, Arthur; Chodorov, Edward; Hagen, Uta] (14-0-2554 to 14-0-2564], 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Caldwell, Erskine; Buck, Pearl S.; Robeson, Eslanda Goode; Magidoff, Robert; Shaw, Bruno; Gary, William; Shayon, Robert Louis; Buckmaster, Henrietta] (14-0-2565 to 14-0-2576), 1948-1949 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Tovrov, Orin; Elder, Harry; Garfield, John; Shull, Leo; Kanin, Garson; Crawford, Cheryl; Jaffe, Sam; Saphier, Jimmy] (14-0-2577 to 14-0-2587), 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Yoshida, Shigeru; Ritt, Thomas Francis; Keller, Father James; Webster, Margaret; Knight, Arthur; Cobb, Lee J.; Eldridge, Florence; Bloomgarden, Kermit; Dunnock, Mildred] (14-0-2588 to 14-0-2609), 1949 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Jacobs, Andrew; Lesinski, John; Curran, Joseph; Heisenberg, Dr. Werner; Lysenko, Trofim D.; Urey, Harold C.; Livermore, Frank D.; Fritz, Ernest W.] (14-0-2610 to 14-0-2618), 1949 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Schappes, Morris U.; Hadley, Morris; Bloch, Dr. Joshua; Dulles, John Foster; Murray, Philip; Winston, Henry; Sacher, Harry; Wallace, Henry A.; Lehman, Herbert H.] (14-0-2619 to 14-0-2625), 1949 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Chase, Stuart; Weill, Kurt; Duff, Howard; Fisher, Dorothy Canfield; Cohen, Lester; Taylor, Dr. Harold; Spaulding, Francis T.; Arshan, Dr. Benjamin] (14-0-2645 to 14-0-2649E), 1948-1951 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Nelson, Steve; Fox, Irving David; Adler, Larry; Draper, Paul; Brown, Irving; Dewey, Thomas E.; Dulles, John Foster; Lehman, Herbert H.] (14-0-2626 to 14-0-2634), 1948-1949 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Eisenhower, Dwight D.; Kasenkina, Oksana Stepanovna; Stevens, Alexander; Pressman, Lee; Abt, John J.; Witt, Nathan; Flynn, Elizabeth Gurley; Hays, Arthur Garfield] (14-0-2635 to 14-0-2644), 1948-1950 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Ratliff, James; Scott, Cecil Donald; Ferrer, Jose; Jory, Victor; McCambridge, Mercedes] (14-0-2650 to 14-0-2653), 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Wallace, Henry A.; Acheson, Dean; Branting, Sonia; Tamris, Helen; Kazan, Elia; Stassen, Harold E.; Powell, Adam Clayton; Giua, Michele; Lunden, Mimi Sverdrup; Hutchinson, H. Lester] (14-0-2654 to 14-0-2660), 1946, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Marcantonio, Vito; Isacson, Leo; Lewis, Sinclair; O'Dwyer, William; Mulligan, Thomas F.; Hall, Pierson M.; McTernan, John; Peck, James] (14-0-2661 to 14-0-2671), 1948-1949 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Fifield, Dr. L. Wendell; Ferguson, Dr. Milton J.; Bruchhausen, Walter; Levinthal, Israel H.; Keogh, J. Vincent; Leech, John H.; Havenner, Frank; Hays, Arthur Garfield; Udell, Margaret K.] (14-0-2672 to 14-0-2675), 1948 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lavery, Emmet G.; Woltman, Frederick; Meng, Dr. John J.; Smith, Reverend Ignatius; Gideonse, Dr. Harry G.; Hopper, Hedda; Bowie, Reverend W. Russell; Nussbaum, David W.; Flakser, Harold] (14-0-2676 to 14-0-2681), 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Fielding, Benjamin; Harris, Helen M.; Kenny, Robert W.; Wallace, Henry A.; Rogge, O. John; Schultz, Rabbi Benjamin; Tito, Marshal; De Lacy, Betty Marie] (14-0-2682 to 14-0-2687), 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Vandenberg, Arthur H.; Ferguson, Homer; Barsov, Anatol; Pirogov, Peter; Swanstrom, Edward E.; Blackett, Patrick M.S.; Osborn, Frederick H.; Ring, William E.; Nussbaum, David W.] (14-0-2688 to 14-0-2695), 1948-1949 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Yankwich, Leon R.; Pearson, Drew; Birkhead, Leon M.; Robeson, Paul; Tolstoy, Alexandra; Jerome, V.J.; Close, Upton; Hughes, Langston; Bontemps, Arna] (14-0-2696 to 14-0-2704), 1948-1949 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Nathan, Edgar J. III; Glasser, Harold; Levine, Isaac Don; McBride, Mary Margaret; Buck, Pearl S.; Robeson, Eslande Goode; White, Dr. Walter; Schlesinger, Dr. Arthur, Jr.] (14-0-2705 to 14-0-2709), 1948-1949 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Fischer, Louis; Browder, Earl; Cowley, Malcolm; Kaye, Danny; University of Washington Professors; Bonte, Florimond; Bottcher, Herman; Yankwich, Leon R.] (14-0-2710 to 14-0-2721), 1947-1951 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Young, John Orr; Garfield, John; Drumheller, Joseph; Bienz, Thomas H.; Quill, Michael J.; Davis, Benjamin J.; O'Connell, Jerry; Clark, Irving, Jr.] (14-0-2722 to 14-0-2730), 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lists of Authors, Educators, and Publishers; Untermeyer, Joseph; Zarichny, James; Wallace, Henry A.; Feldman, Justin; White, Dr. Mary G.; Rubin, Isadore] (14-0-2731 to 14-0-2747), 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Blankfort, Michael; Carlson, Evans; Bryson, Hugh; Jenkins, David; Bridges, Harry; Cole, Lester; Dunn, John; Gentile, Danny; Thomas, J. Parnell; Belfrage, Cedric] (14-0-2748 to 14-0-2758), 1948-1949 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Brainin, Joseph; Russell, Maud; Ashe, Harold J.; Quill, Michael J.; Cameron, Angus; Wallace, Henry A.; Yergan, Dr. Max; Jay, Elsie; Moore, Jim; Lazorek, Elizabeth; Rosenblum, Irwin] (14-0-2759 to 14-0-2770), 1946-1951 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Banning, Margaret Culkin; Josephson, Matthew; Ross, Allan; Cahn, Ira L.; Baruchin, Oscar; Fine, Sylvia; Matthews, J.B.; Calver, Homer N.; Kanin, Garson] (14-0-2771 to 14-0-2774E), 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Alvarez; Addis; Clubb; Lederman; Paley; Livingston; Schneider; Meadows; Hertz; Bay] (14-0-2775 to 14-0-2783), 1948-1951 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Budenz; Birkhead; Bachrach; Bell; Billings; Baldwin; Brock; Bullitt; Bridger; Klein; Acheson] (14-0-2784 to 14-0-2797), 1941-1951 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Strong; Chamberlin; Clair; Chodorov; Worsby; Crosby; Izvestia; Chevalier; Carlson; Brown; Bittner; Batterson; Belfrage; Campbell; Clark; Bales] (14-0-2798 to 14-0-2817), 1947-1951 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Kelton; Bell; Keane; Downes; Untermeyer; Bernstein; Robson; McAffery; Connelly; Klein; Meredith; Gordon; Kanin; Webster] (14-0-2818 to 14-0-2839), 1950 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Patton; Harburg; Fortas; Schachter; De Koyen; Grossman; Rocca; de Mauriac; Wagner; Independent Socialist League; De Los Rios; Gilbert; Wallace; Straus; Foster] (14-0-2840 to 14-0-2854), 1948-1951 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Levin; Cherrington; Givens; Acheson; Donner; Phillips; Robinson; Straight; Fast; Wren; Andrews; Brecht] (14-0-2855 to 14-0-2874A), 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Holdridge; Genn; Powers; Day; Warren; Da Silva; Watson; Dean; Gruenberg] (14-0-2875 to 14-0-2887), 1947-1951 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Reiss; Phillips; Bernstein; Shaw; Untermeyer; Merrill; Hulter; Bromberg; Klein; Staw; Randolph; Roosevelt; Fry; Petree] (14-0-2888 to 14-0-2900), 1949-1951 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Woodbury; the Weavers; Shields; Chamberlin; Brothman; Bern; Collins; Chaplin; Ives; Cvetic; Glazek; Garland; Neylan; Baran] (14-0-2901 to 14-0-2921), 1949-1951 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Sanders; Zaidenberg; Sauber; Douglas; Commorre; Weissberg; Werner; White; Wicker; William; Woodruff] (14-0-2922 to 14-0-2932), 1932-1950 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Tortosa; Boyzcum; Ingram; Ashe; Lauterbach; Sacher; Isserman; Kilgallen; Kolmar; Kent; Snow] (14-0-2933 to 14-0-2949), 1949-1951 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Bromberg, J. Edward; Blackwell, Jack; Graze, Cyril; Donner, Robert; Mather, Professor Kirtley S.; Rice, Elmer; Murdock, William; Alpenfels, Ethel J.] (14-0-2950 to 14-0-2966), 1950-1952 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Merrill, Lewis G.; Marshall, George C.; Kalinin, Mikhail I.; Garramone, Michael; Godoff, Elliot; Foreman, Carl; Dobie, Professor J. Frank] (14-0-2967 to 14-0-2977), 1937, 1946-1952 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Ropes, Ernest C.; Wright, Archie; Riesel, Victor; Tead, Dr. Ordway; Stoddard, George D.; Roberts, Jack; Pious, Minerva; Perl, Arnold] (14-0-2978 to 14-0-2989), 1948-1951 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Chase, Allan; Mather, Professor Kirtley F.; Pressman, David; Fritchman, Reverend Stephen H.; Shaw, Irwin; Sheean, Vincent; Pope, Arthur Upham; Carter, Edward C.] (14-0-2990 to 14-0-2997), 1949-1952 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Sloane, Allan; Limon, Jose; Schick, Dr. Bela; Pappas, George Demetrios; Hiss, Alger; Matusow, Harvey M.; Graze, Cyril; Buckley, William F., Jr.] (14-0-2998 to 14-0-3014), 1951-1952 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Brown, Owen B.; Siegmeister, Elie; Chaplin, Charlie; Vincent, John Carter; Budenz, Louis; Gellhorn, Professor Walter; Reid, Dr. Ira De A.; Mather, Professor Kirtley F.; Dulles, John Foster] (14-0-3015 to 14-0-3024), 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Emerson, Thomas Irwin; Emerson, Dr. Haven; Hays, Paul R.; Holm, Hanya; Burke, Robert; Ace, Goodman; San Giovani, Dominick; Ascoli, Max] (14-0-3025 to 14-0-3032), 1952 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Leonard, Richard T.; Sturges, Wesley Alba; Alpenfels, Ethel J.; Goff, Kenneth; Fishko, Sol; Gardner, Ava; Gould, Kenneth M.; Celler, Emanuel] (14-0-3033 to 14-0-3042), 1952 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Verano, Sam; Wilson, Dr. Philip Duncan; Young, Coleman; Krutch, Joseph Wood; Parks, Samuel Joseph, Jr.; Kubie, Lawrence C.; Luccock, Halford E.] (14-0-3043 to 14-0-3049), 1952 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lorant, Stefan; Barile, Pat; Untermeyer, Louis; Ryan, Lawrence; Scott, Evelyn; Yrka, Blanche; Offie, Carmel; Van Doren, Carl; Sloane, Marcella] (14-0-3050 to 14-0-3059), 1952 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Ramsey, David; Drake, Alfred; Peck, Seymour; McGinley, Phyllis; Aaron, Dr. Harold; France, Clemens J.] (14-0-3060 to 14-0-3065), 1951-1953 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Chaplin, Charlie; Montagu, M.F. Ashley; McHenry, Professor Dean Eugene; Marx, Groucho; Mayer, Dr. Leo; Paris, Jerry; Rogers, John; Scourby, Alexander; Suhl, Yuri; Waller, Theodore; Bolton, Harold; Watson, Professor Goodwin; Hiken, Nat; Kilburn, Terrence (Terry); Rosenberg, Isadore; Maisel, Albert Q.; Faggen, Harold; Hausner, Jerry] (14-0-3066 to 14-0-3083), 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Tushnet, Dr. Leonard; Crowther, Bosley; Agar, Herbert; Brown, Frank H.; Karr, David; Dundes, Jules; Fisher, Dorothy Canfield; Gilbreth, Charles; Gesell, Dr. Arnold; Bliss, Ted; Priestly, J.B.; Pottish, Morris; Porter; Dozenberg, Nicholas; Wallach, Eli; Ernst, Morris L.; Zablodowsky, David; Mather; Neuberger, Samuel A.; Askew; Lefkowitz, Irving (Lefty); Weyl, Nathaniel; Heald, Henry T.; Zworykin, Dr. V. K.; Schwartz; Vincent, John Carter; Sqadrilli, Alexander E.; Kellar, Dr. Joseph Bishop; Cole, David L.; Copland, Aaron; Thierman, Lieutenant Sheppard Carl] (14-0-3084 to 14-0-3112), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lilleleht, Lembit U.; Michael, Sandra; Friedman, Irving S.; Lattimore, Owen; Barnes, Joe; Menges, Karl; Bradley; Crouse, Russel; Daugherty, James; Janeway, Elizabeth (Hall); Kantor, MacKinlay; Sheean, Vincent (James); Reynolds, Quentin; Brown, John Mason; Clark, Walter Van Tilburg; Adams, Samuel Hopkins; Wolfe, James H.] (14-0-3113 to 14-0-3125), 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Hilton; Marchand; Ledoux; Hathaway; Chu Tong; Geismar; Index of Clergy and Rabbis; Woodcock; Taylor; Spaeth; Fischer; Dietz; Paradise; Sabin; Scott; Buitenkant; Bodde; Morrison; Hudson; Bradshaw; Jackson; Haber; Drake; Bohrod; Schretber; Blanch; Dehn; Shortall; Joliot-Curie; Lauterbach; Smith] (14-0-3126 to 14-0-3159), 1947-1953 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lothrop, Reverend Donald G.; Brown, Professor Emily C.; Carpenter, Reverend J. Henry; Boudin, Leonard; Stern, Bernhard J.] (14-0-3160 to 14-0-3164), 1940s-1950s (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Parker; Lockwood; Kettering; Benedict; Weltfish; Stewart] (14-0-3165 to 14-0-3168), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Sokol; National Citizens Commission for the Public Schools (list); Eby; Frichtman; Kaye; Gray; Jakstys; Viertel; Chodorov; Porter; Logsdon] (14-0-3169 to 14-0-3179), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Miller; Burlingham; Belafonte; Russell; Rosenberg; Greenberg; Beiler; Voss; Murdock; Seymour; Duncan; Holden; Perrin; Mann; Rothenberg; Aver; Simon; Luccock; Mayer; Prisoners of War] (14-0-3180 to 14-0-3200), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Smodroff, Hazel; Parkchester Evictees; Atkinson, William; Lothrop, Donald G.; Levenson, Samuel; Cooper, Gary; Hamilton, Helen; Bourneuf, Philip; Wood, Peggy; Marr, Joe; Vaughn, Sarah; Gibb, MacGregor; Fitzgerald, Ella; Balsam, Martin; Overstreet, Bonaro Wilkinson; Overstreet, Harry Allen; Fox, Sidney; Kelly, Gene] (14-0-3201 to 14-0-3218), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Niebuhr; Shishkin; Straus; Fleisher; Blanding; Taylor; Gregg; Lyon; Clapper; Meyer; Roper; Lefferts; Wilson; Schwartz; Ocko; Oppenheimer; Dryden; Williams; Heine; Stein; Andren; Hart; Robert; Petroff; Cohn; Silverman; Miller; Mayer] (14-0-3219 to 14-0-3246), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Friedman, Anne; Stein, Peter; Gould, Kenneth M.; Beal, John; Murname, Francis; McCarthy, Joe; Carroll, Sidney; Hall, Helen; Conant, James; Clark, Evans; Davis, Chester C.; Francis; Bunche, Ralph J.; Hoffman, Paul Gray; Shuster, George N.; Myers, William Irving] (14-0-3247 to 14-0-3263), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Menkin; Obler; Individuals in Dramatic Workshop; Hall; Lewis; Tandy; Brando; Baker; Douglas; Kirkpatrick; Pusey; Phelps; King; Berle; Aaron; Saron] (14-0-3264 to 14-0-3283), 1949-1953 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Eisenhower, Dwight D.; Bjerkholt, Hans; Einstein, Dr. Albert; Connorton, John V.; Pusey, Nathan Marsh; Silverman, Allan E. (a.k.a. Allan E. Sloane); Sloane, Robert; Lechner, Dr. John R.; Loomer, Bernard M.; Moon, Bucklin; Wuchinich, George S.; Rogers, Will, Jr.] (14-0-3284 to 14-0-3297), 1945-1953 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Sulzberger; Pell; Conant; Gordis; Gilbert; Hunter; Brando; Thornhill; Sayers; Riess; Baehr; Milosz; Griswold; Seymour] (14-0-3298 to 14-0-3320), 1953; 2014.082 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Jenner; Bettis; Dodd; Penn; Blaustein; Wuchinich; Bortz; Marshall; Lee; Atwater; Harrington; Hudson; Goldman; Gold; Portuondo; Peck] (14-0-3321 to 14-0-3344), 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Johnson; Meyer; Fine; Compton; Martin; Sherover; Mosely; Perl; Dohrenwend; Klineberg; Mather; MacGowan; Mann; Kazan; Lewis; Kreisler; Rickenbacker; Reed; Rosen; Rapport; Poston; Patterson; Morris; Wolfe; Lewis; Conant; Stern; Dodds; Geisse] (14-0-3345 to 14-0-3380), 1949-1953 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Spewack, Bella and Sam; List of Vassar Professors; Peck, Gregory; Flynn, John; Conant, Dr. James B.; Charles, Richard] (14-0-3381 to 14-0-3388), 1949-1953 (Box 16, Folder 17)